[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the largest of Uranus moons?", "correct_answer": "Titania.", "incorrect_answers": ["Miranda.", "Ariel.", "Oberon."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This dog breed, developed in England, has an egg-shaped head, small eyes, and very strong muscular body with smooth short fur and short legs.", "correct_answer": "Bull Terrier", "incorrect_answers": ["Cairn Terrier", "English Shepherd", "Wire Fox Terrier"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Queen Elizabeth II was coronated Queen in 1953. Whom did she directly succeed?", "correct_answer": "George VI", "incorrect_answers": ["Edward VIII", "George V", "Elizabeth Bowes-Lyon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Soviet agent is the villain in the movie For Your Eyes Only.", "correct_answer": "Aristotle Kristatos", "incorrect_answers": ["Borislav  Vadic", "Joao Pereira", "Laszlo Falkenstein"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following terms describes a dark layer of clouds that bring rain or snow?", "correct_answer": "Nimbostratus", "incorrect_answers": ["Stratocumulus", "Cirrus", "Altocumulus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Frank Zappas daughter?", "correct_answer": "Moon Unit", "incorrect_answers": ["Dweezil", "Moon Beam", "Elektra Moon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was the first ostrich farm built in the USA?", "correct_answer": "1886", "incorrect_answers": ["1906", "1956", "1926"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was Wonder Bread  first marketed in the USA as pre-sliced bread?", "correct_answer": "1930", "incorrect_answers": ["1934", "1926", "1925"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Beagles are sometimes used for termite detection in Australia.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The sphygmomanometer is a device invented by Samuel Siegfried Karl Ritter von Basch, used to measure what?", "correct_answer": "Blood pressure", "incorrect_answers": ["Myopia", "Intensity of headaches", "Heart murmurs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Bible, he was the first person mentioned to be put into jail.", "correct_answer": "Joseph", "incorrect_answers": ["Barabas", "Jeremiah", "Daniel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How old was Anne Bancroft (Mrs. Robinson) during the filming of The Graduate?", "correct_answer": "36", "incorrect_answers": ["45", "43", "40"]}]